<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Auto Everything</name>
  <author>gookeryoung</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>gookeryoung.autoeverything</packageId>
  <description>智能自动万物管理 MOD，为殖民者自动执行人员评级、工作优先级分配与高价值单位标记。

三大功能：
- 人员自动评级：按 SSS/SS/S/A/B/C/D/X 八档评级，可选应用评级前缀到名字并重排殖民者栏。综合射击/近战/工作/社交/特质等维度，配偶评级豁免，自定义评级覆盖。
- 工作自动配置：按工作类别与兴趣/技能多遍协调分配工作优先级。紧急工作全员优先，关键/普通/次级专业工作保底 2 人，研究保底 1 人，辅助工作按评级分档。事件驱动 + 2500 tick 冷却 + 战斗中延迟执行避免打断手术。
- 高价值自动标记：为 S+ 档次所有人类单位（殖民者/奴隶/囚犯/敌对/中立/盟友/野生）头顶实时绘制彩色星标，按类别区分颜色，便于一眼识别高价值目标。

零配置开箱即用，每个殖民者根据技能与特质自动识别角色与评级。兼容大多数 MOD，支持存档中途添加。

English: Intelligent auto-everything management MOD. Automatically performs colonist rating, work priority allocation, and high-value pawn marking for colonists.

Three main features:
- Auto Tier: rates colonists into SSS/SS/S/A/B/C/D/X tiers, optionally applies tier prefix to names and reorders the colonist bar. Comprehensive evaluation across shooting/melee/work/social/traits, spouse tier exemption, custom tier override.
- Auto Work: allocates work priorities via multi-pass coordinated allocation by work category, passion and skill. Emergency work prioritized for all; key/normal/secondary skill work guarantees 2 people; research guarantees 1; service work tiered by rating. Event-driven + 2500 tick cooldown + deferred during combat to avoid interrupting surgery.
- Auto Mark Pawn: draws colored star markers above all humanlike pawns of S+ tier (colonists/slaves/prisoners/enemies/neutral/ally/wild) in real time, color-coded by category for quick identification of high-value targets.

Zero config, works out of the box. Each colonist auto-detected by skill and trait. Compatible with most mods. Safe to add mid-save.</description>
  <modIconPath>UI/Icons/ModIcon</modIconPath>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>ludeon.rimworld</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
